# 哈喽大家好 我们今天把锅这些东西买过来了
Hey guys, we bought these kitchenware today like the woks
# 买了6个锅
Six woks
# 然后还有一些其他的宽油盆啊
And other stuff like the pots for Kuanyou (oil pots)
# 这些也到了 陆陆续续到了
They are all here gradually
# 现在我就把这里面收拾一下
Now I’m going to clean up the place
# 该弄得弄 然后该摆的摆
Put everything at the right place
# 大概过两天就应该可以做饭吃了这里
Then the place should be ready to cook in about two days
# 这里面全是宽油盆
These are the pots for Kuanyou
# 先放地上吧
Leave them on the floor for now
# 现在师傅已经帮我们把这些配件都拿过来了
Now the delivery guys have got the parts here
# 锅也拿过来了
Along with the woks
# 现在的话就把这个拆了
Now let’s open it
# 这个拆了 然后把这个胶纸撕掉
And peel off the films
# 也挺多的 有几个打荷台 有灶呀还有不锈钢的那个东西
A lot of stuff here including the prep tables, stoves and the stainless steel stuff
# 把它撕完了之后再把地上的扫一下
Let’s peel the films and sweep the floor
# 然后应该再过个几天这里就可以开火了
Then we can cook in here in a few days
# 我先来撕一个 看看这个好不好撕
Let me peel one first to see whether it comes off easily
# 这个很简单 一下子就撕掉了
There you go, pretty easy
# 撕完了之后这里不锈钢的看起来很干净
With the films gone, these stainless steel surfaces look so clean
# 这一个的话是用来装调料的
This cabinet is for the seasoning
# 里面全部放调料盆
We’ll put the seasoning containers in here
# 然后这个我们下了班之后这个可以把它盖起来
The cabinet can be closed like this after work
# 这样子就可以防止蟑螂跑进去 或者老鼠
Thus it keeps the roaches and rats out
# 然后这个灶台的纸应该比较难撕一点
The films on the stoves are hard to come off
# 慢慢来
Let’s take it slow
# 好了 这个就撕好了
Alright, all the peelings on this done
# 撕完了之后看起来干干净净
It seems so clean and tidy after peeling
# 还不错 现在就慢慢的去撕这些
Nice, let’s move on the others
# 等一下还有几个同事一起来帮我弄
A few colleagues are coming to help me
# 我先一个人慢慢做着
Let me start first
# 现在我们这个上面还有2个洞
There are two empty slots up there
# 我准备用这个去给它补一下
I’m going to fill those with these
# 刚才那个叔叔借了我一个锯子 给它锯成了2块
That nice uncle lent me a saw to cut it into two pieces
# 行了
Alright
# 下一个
Next one
# 这样刚好 因为这个也是旧的
Nice fit, this fence is used
# 我就将就它这个旧的安上去
Let’s give it another place to shine
# 现在就可以了
Nice
# 就是等一下我们再大扫除把它搞干净一点
Next we are going to clean up the place
# 今天我们把这个膜啊这些都撕好了
Today we peeled all the films on the appliances
# 这个灶台我们3个人也把它搬好了
We three also moved the stoves to the right places
# 然后打荷台啊这些也弄好了 地上也弄干净了
The prep tables are also in the right places and we swept the floor
# 现在就等着明天再搞精细一点 搞干净一点这些卫生
Tomorrow we’ll do stuffs with more details. Clean up everything
# 然后估计再过一个星期就可以开火了
And then the place should be ready to cook in a week
# 好啦本期视频就到这里了 拜拜
Alright that’s it for this episode. Bye!